CRISTIAN EZEQUIEL LA NEVE

Address: Morón, Buenos Aires, Argentina. E-mail: lanevecristianezequiel@gmail.com

Contact: +54 9 11 2465-5934

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ezelnv/

Github: https://github.com/Feegaer

ABOUT ME

I have been working as a system analyst for the last three years developing web pages and web applications using TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, SASS, ReactJS and Bootstrap.

Besides, I've been working with NodeJS, .NET, ExpressJS and ASP.NET developing web services, debugging code, building API REST from scratch and maintaining it also providing IT support to companies like Naturgy BAN S.A., MetroGas and Gasnor.

What's more, I have knowledge of GNU/Linux distributions (UNRAID, ProxMox, Debian 10 and Debian 11) for server maintenance and management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Exgadet S.A.

Customers: Naturgy BAN S.A., MetroGas, Gasnor y Deyel.

System Analyst - Feb 2023 - Present

Software development

- API Rest development for Deyel Company with NodeJS and ExpressJS for system integrations.
- Web application development for internal use with ReactJS, TypeScript, CSS3, ViteJS and HTML5.
- Web application development for external use for MetroGas Company.
- Web services development for Naturgy BAN S.A. company using .NET and NodeJS to communicate tasks.

Infrastructure and DevOps

- GNU/Linux (Debian, Ubuntu) servers management.
- Server virtualization with ProxMox.
- VPN, network mapping and access rules configuration with FortiGate.
- Process automatization to communicate with customers for Naturgy BAN S.A. company with API from Zenvia.

Technical process documentation, network topologies and manuals.

Management and IT support

- Support of second grade to users
- Technical and no technical personal capacitation.

System assistant- Jun 2022 - Feb 2023

- Web development and support for Exgadet S.A., Nortenergy S.R.L and Naturgy BAN S.A. companies with PHP7, HTML5, CSS3, SASS and JavaScript.
- Repair, building and maintenance of PC and servers.
- Mobile configuration and PC for administrative use.
- Database management with MSSQL and MySQL.
- CRUD system development

Freelance

Web development and design - Apr 2021 - Jun 2022

- Web development for startups and SME with PHP, HTML5, CSS3 and MySQL.
- Web maintenance and support for customers.

EDUCATION

- NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF LA MATANZA Computing Engineering (2022 - Present)
- HIGH SCHOOL N° 23, "ADOLFO SALDÍAS"
 Bachelor of Humanities (2017 2018)
- TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL N° 8 DE MORÓN Electronic Technician (2010 - 2016)

TECH ABILITIES

- Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript, Visual Basic, .NET v PHP
- Frameworks: ExpressJS, ReactJS y Bootstrap
- Database: MySQL, MSSQL y SQLite
- Tools: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Postman, GIT y PUTTY
- Others: ProxMox, FortiGate, GNU/Linux distributions management, etc.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- English: B1 Intermediate / B2 High according to EF